Hey what's up what are you doing
I'm studying for the history test Tomorrow
and finishing the math homework
what about you?
Same
Well I'm also cleaning my room
and I'm talking to Maria on Facebook
Do you know what will be on the test?
Well
I'm studying World War 1 and World War 2
OH thanks, Well I'm trying to study
But I don't remember anything we learned
Wait A second my sister is being so annoying
She's playing her music too loud
Grace, turn down the music!
Okay
I'm listening now
Oh
I Was Just saying that
I'm trying to study,
But I don't remember anything we learned
Well I'm checking my old history notes to remember what we learned in class
You should do the same
That 's a Good idea
But first I have to find my notebook
What you think Marissa and Lola are doing to study for the test
I think they organized a study group and they are studying together with Sam and Nina in Starbucks now
That's a good idea
But I would get too distracted I can't even study alone at home
I'm downloading the new CSI episode and
I'm listening To the new Taylor Swift album
Are you even studying for the test at all dilara
I know I'm trying to study
But it's just so boring
Are you studying a lot for this test
YES, I am I know it's boring
We will be up all night studying for this test
We better start now
We are getting too distracted when we talk to each other
We are turning everything off and we are going to focus on studying for the test
Okay
See you tomorrow
Good luck on the test
Thanks
You too,
Bye