I have to study every week so I have only Sunday off
I go to
School every morning
Sometimes I study even on Sunday
I'm so busy but now I'm attending an English
class in the evening
Passing the evening
When I have  free Time
Time
I love reading books
Newspapers and listening to music
There are many kinds of music statues Rock
How many kinds of music statues Rock
Dance Etc
sometimes I go shopping with my friends but my favorite hobby is speaking English
I started to
Speak English when I came to University English center 2 weeks ago
Speak English when I came to University English Venta 2 weeks
#Stegall
Now I can speak English everywhere
Every time and I want to say "I love English so much"
Every time and they want to say I love English